MAN 1 [ OVER PA ] : Good morning , Presage employees .
We hope you 're all ready for our exciting team-building retreat .
Please enjoy your breakfast ...
and then make your way to the bus , which will leave shortly .
Hey , Sam , when I said , " Would you put breakfast together for the retreat ? " ...
I meant , like , some stale doughnuts , some coffee .
But this is amazing .
Thanks , man . Just remember that when you see my sales report for last month .
Oh , I saw it last night .
Shit . Has Dennis seen it ?
Not yet .
Look , you just need to make a decision , you know ?
Are you gonna be " chef " or are you gonna be " sales guy " ?
I 'm saying that as your friend because , as your boss , I 'm ready to fire your ass .
- As your friend , I appreciate that advice . - Good .
[ EVERCLEAR 'S " I WILL BUY YOU A NEW LIFE " PLAYING ON STEREO ]
Inside my baby 's room
Hold on , man , I 'll be right back .
Yeah , I guess I 'm doing okay
I moved in with ...
[ MUSIC STOPS ]
SAM : Molly . Your ticket 's canceled .
Tell me that 's a mistake .
I was gonna tell you after this weekend .
Uh , tell me what ?
That I don 't think it 's such a good idea .
What , the trip ? it 's my brother 's wedding .
What 's going on here ?
We should talk about this later . Let 's just ...
What , pretend like I didn 't see this for the next two days ? No , let 's talk about this .
It 's not working out , Sam .
We 're not working out .
Hey .
Hey . Oh , it 's , uh , Candice , right ?
- Not funny . - Oh ...
Okay , sorry , this is not a vacation . Okay , this is a business retreat .
So we 're gonna be all business for the next two days .
Sorry .
I love you , but doesn 't change the fact that you 're still an intern .
[ CANDICE SIGHS ]
Oh , um , but that 12 : 30 curfew tonight ? You should plan on breaking that .
Why ?
For the naked team-building .
[ LAUGHS ]
[ IN AUSTRALIAN ACCENT ] Hey , Olivia .
Don 't forget these .
Oh , yeah . I keep trying to .
- Hmm . - I like it. it 's very Lisa Loeb .
Oh , well , you know ...
I 'd rather be very Olivia .
We got a gig on Sunday .
Yeah , I 'll be there .
Morning , Peter .
- Looking good . - Uh , hi .
Olivia . Have you slept with every hipster in town yet ?
Candice . Do you actually get paid for this internship ...
or does Daddy just increase your allowance ?
You know , if you wanna get rid of that baby fat , you should try the gym .
They have these workout machines that you use on your back .
You 're good at that .
Sweetie , it 's not fat .
They 're called tits .
You 're not looking so hot there , Moll-face .
Gee , thanks .
Did you try the little jam-bread whatever your boyfriend made ?
I gotta tell you , he 's a pre ... Uh-oh , that 's what it is , is it ? Did I touch a nerve ?
- Just leave me alone , Isaac . - Hey , Moll ? Moll ? Look at me .
If you ever need anyone to talk to ...
[ CELL PHONE RINGING ]
I 've been told I 'm a good listener by a lot of ladies . Shh , wait .
Tell me this is Kimber from last Tuesday . Wait , I 'm sorry , which Kimber is ... ?
Hey , let 's sit next to each other on the bus .
No , no , I remember you . You were , like , a bigger gal , right ?
You know what you should do ? You should apologize .
- Why ? - Doesn 't matter .
Never matters . " I 'm sorry , because I ... "
[ HORN HONKING ]
Oh , shit .
Hey , Stan , how 's it going ?
Uh , it 's Sam , sir .
Did you just correct me ?
SAM [ STAMMERS ] : No .
Look at me .
- What 's my name ? - Dennis .
Look away .
All set , Pete ?
Yes , sir . Yeah , we 're just waiting on Nathan .
What 's the one thing we can 't recycle , Pete ?
Wasted time , sir .
Exactly . I wanna be on the road in 90 seconds .
Uh , well , I just saw his car , so I 'll go track him down .
Way to show some initiative , Stan .
It 's gonna be a good day .
SAM : Hey , guys . MAN 1 : Hey , man .
SAM : What 's up , bud ?
MAN : Why you riding Nate so hard , man ?
ROY : You know , I 'm just trying to make sense of it here .
Three weeks ago they brought you in as assistant plant manager ...
and now you got a day off ? - It 's not a day off. it 's a re ... Re ...
Re ... Re-what ? Retarded ?
It 's a retreat .
NATHAN : I don 't wanna go . I 'm just following orders .
- So if you don 't like it , then you can ... ROY : I can what ? What ? I can what ?
Nathan , hey . Come on , man , we 're all waiting for you .
- Yeah , okay . - Now , hold on . What you gonna say ?
What you gonna say ?
I got 15 years on you here . You got , what , four years in some classroom upstate ?
Listen , if you think I 'm gonna sit here ...
Not a good idea , Roy . Not a good idea , man .
We 're fine for the day .
Why do you let him get away with that ?
No choice . He 's the union rep .
I fire him and suddenly I 've got a factory full of Roys .
But I 'll win him over , even if it kills me .
What about you ?
When are they gonna offer you that permanent gig at the restaurant ?
- They already did . - Dude , that 's great .
SAM : I don 't know , man .
I mean , they wanna send me to the flagship restaurant in Paris ...
for who knows how long ? Could be six months , could be a year .
I just thought I 'd be leaving too much behind .
Although now I 'm not so sure .
Well , look , if you do go to Paris , do me a favor .
- What 's that ? - Take Roy with you .
Aw , hell , no .
[ KNOCKING ]
NATHAN : Hey , Sam .
You coming ?
Yeah .
MAN [ ON TV ] : Get ready for a new adventure at 180 Corporate Consulting .
For the next two days , you will be tested , both physically and mentally ...
to help you reach your true potential ...
through working as part of your corporate team .
This weekend , a professional will guide you to achieving better results ...
What are those for ?
Oh , it 's , um , just something I do to relax me . And for luck .
Gymnasts are worse than baseball players at this kind of thing .
She 's superstitious .
[ CELL PHONE RINGING ]
Hey , Katrina , how you doing ?
Nah , just this stupid retreat thing with the idiots from the office .
No , no , no , not you , sir . Them .
Hold on a sec , let me go someplace a little more private .
Bald 's the new black , sir . Bald 's the new black .
Yeah , no , hang on a sec , babe . Just gonna head on back to my private office .
[ MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY ON TV ]
WORKER : The right-hand side !
Whew .
Ow . Damn it .
MAN [ ON TV ] : For management , the valuable skills necessary ...
for being a good leader will be cultivated through a variety ...
[ ON RADIO ] Dust in the wind
All we are ...
WORKER 1 : We 'll tie it off from the far side .
WORKER 2 : Oh , whoa !
WORKER 3 : Whoa , what the hell ?
[ RATTLING ]
- Peter , did you feel that ? - What ?
Something 's wrong .
WORKER 4 : Look out !
SAM : Molly , come on . - Candice .
WORKER 4 : Go ! WORKER 5 : Go , go !
Candice ! Candice !
CANDICE : Peter !
Peter ! Peter !
PETER : No , Candice ! Aah !
[ SCREAMING ]
No !
[ WHIMPERING ]
Peter ! Come on , Peter , let 's go !
Molly , come on !
What the fuck ? !
[ ALL YELLING ]
SAM : Oh , no ! No ! No !
Come on , let 's go ! Let 's go !
[ GRUNTING ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ BOTH GRUNTING ]
OLIVIA : Oh , Shit !
SAM : Over here ! See the railing ?
You can do this . Let 's go .
Let 's go . Do it !
You can do it . Don 't look down !
Good . Good .
[ CABLE SNAPS ]
MAN 1 : Run !
OLIVIA : Help me !
- Sam ! - Olivia !
Olivia !
OLIVIA : Sam ! - I 'm right here . I 'm right here . Okay .
MAN 2 : It 's coming loose !
SAM : Do you feel it ? All right . MOLLY : Olivia , come on .
SAM : it 's okay , it 's safe . Now you 've just gotta follow this to Molly 's voice , all right ?
Come towards me . Come on , you 're almost there ! Come on .
[ SCREAMS ]
[ GRUNTING ]
Come on .
- Come on . Come on ! - Molly .
[ OLIVIA MOLLY SCREAM ]
No ! No !
[ SCREAMING ]
[ GASPING ]
- Aah ! - Olivia !
NATHAN : Sam ! Wait for us !
Oh , my God !
Sam !
Aah ! Sam , be careful !
[ GRUNTING ]
[ DENNIS SCREAMING ]
[ SIZZLING ]
PETER : Sam !
Peter ! Hurry !
Sam ! Sam !
Sam !
[ ALL SCREAMING ]
MOLLY : Hold on !
Come on , come on .
[ MOLLY SCREAMS ]
Sam , hold on !
[ YELLS ]
[ SAM YELLS ]
MOLLY : No ! Peter !
[ BANGING AND CREAKING ]
[ SCREAMS ]
[ PANTING ]
Ow . Damn it .
MAN [ ON TV ] : - - as well as define controls and procedures .
We will help you build a culture of corporate ethics by defining ...
[ ON RADIO ] Dust in the wind
MAN [ ON TV ] : - - risk management process .
We all gotta get off .
What are you talking about ?
- The bridge is gonna collapse . - What ?
- We 're all gonna die . - What the hell is going on ?
We 're all gonna die if we don 't get off this bridge now !
Stan , relax , it 's just some construction .
Molly , please . Please , God , follow me .
Open the door .
This is a major liability issue . If something happens to them , it 's on us , you get that ?
- Yeah . - Then go get that .
Yeah . Yeah , yeah , all right .
Hey , Sam ? Molly ?
SAM : Peter , please , just follow . PETER : Come on !
Okay , everybody just calm down .
- I 'm gonna go help . - Please don 't .
PETER : Hey , guys , come on !
SAM : Let 's go !
PETER : Sam , just get back on the bus . We can talk about it .
Molly , Sam , come on , guys .
Did he seem weird to you when he got on the bus ?
No , he was fine . It 's like he just snapped .
- What 's going on ? - What the hell is going on out here ?
[ CABLES SNAPPING ]
DENNIS : We should , uh ...
ISAAC : Holy shit !
DENNIS : Get off the bus !
[ CROWD SCREAMING ]
SAM : Come on !
How did you know ?
MAN : That 's the big question here .
It says right here in your statement :
" I saw it collapse . I knew it would happen . "
That sounds premeditated to me .
No , no , no . That 's not what I meant .
I had a vision .
Okay . A vision .
Psychic phenomena , ghosts , Bigfoot .
You actually believe in that stuff ?
I don 't know .
I 'll tell you what I believe :
There 's an answer for everything .
There 's an answer for why you knew to warn everyone ...
the bridge was going to collapse , and minutes later , it did .
I told you , I saw it coming . I don 't know how .
I just did .
And no one else did ?
Like I said , it just came out of nowhere .
Did Sam have issues with authority ?
Did he ever demonstrate any sort of extremist behavior ?
No .
Wait . " Extremist behavior " ' ?
You mean like a terrorist ?
You see him talk to anyone that morning ? On a cell phone , pay phone ?
Just his girlfriend .
His ex-girlfriend , I mean . Molly .
- But that was in person . - Molly .
Ex .
BLOCK : Tell me about the breakup .
Was he upset ? Scale of 1 to 10 .
It 's personal .
You must have been pissed , right ? Getting dumped like that .
What does that have to do with anything ?
I 'm just trying to get all the pieces of the puzzle together ...
before I start moving them around , making them fit .
Look , I just had a hunch that something bad was gonna happen . That 's it .
[ KNOCKING ON Doom
Excuse me .
Forensics came back with the analysis .
- And ? - They 're chalking it up to high winds ...
and structural damage from the construction .
" High winds " ?
AGENT : Yeah . Send everyone home .
You 're free to go .
I have a feeling we 'll be seeing each other again .
Call it a hunch .
WOMAN [ ON TV ] : Authorities are calling the North Bay Bridge collapse ...
a freak act of nature ...
citing a highway improvement project that may have weakened the superstructure .
Among the survivors were eight employees of Presage Paper ...
on their way to a business retreat .
The other 17 employees were killed in the collapse .
And although they 've been branded the " lucky eight " ...
the surviving employees now face an uncertain future .
NATHAN : Hey , guys .
MOLLY : Hey .
PETER : Hey .
Anybody know when this thing 's supposed to start ?
When Dennis gets here , I guess .
That agent still hounding you ?
No . You heard the news , it was natural causes .
Yeah , more like supernatural .
How you holding up ? I tried calling .
No , yeah , I saw . I was just tired ...
ISAAC : So ?
How did you explain it ?
I didn 't .
I couldn 't .
Sam , there had to be a reason .
Heh . That is exactly what the agent kept saying .
Whatever answer you 're looking for , I don 't have it .
Yeah , Sam 's right . It doesn 't matter how it happened .
We should all just put it behind us and be grateful we 're still alive .
Definitely beats the alternative , right ?
DENNIS : I look out at the faces today ...
and I see family members , friends .
But the people that left us on the bridge that day , they were more than that .
People like Jennifer Alcott ...
Chris Boylan ...
David Buckler .
Maybe you worked next to them .
Maybe you worked for them .
But we all worked with them , huh ?
Who can forget Trevor Wino 's smile ?
Or Isaac Palmer .
Did he just say my name ?
[ OLIVIA SNORTS ]
- That 's not funny . - I know , I 'm sorry .
I just get weird with tragedies . I 'm sorry .
[ WHISPERS ] I see dead people .
[ OLIVIA LAUGHING ]
Guys .
Death ...
doesn 't like to be cheated .
Excuse me ?
What 's that supposed to mean ?
You all just be careful now .
PETER : Okay . Thanks for the advice !
Creepy guy .
[ BLUDWORTH WHISTLING " LEANING ON THE EVERLASTING ARMS " ]
COOK : How 's that foie gras , Sam ? Waiting on you .
[ TERRY POISON 'S " BALLROOM " PLAYING ]
Wasted like a drunk She drank , drunk , drunk
Stop it
It 's not forgotten
COOK 1 : Thanks .
COOK 2 : Got my dessert ?
[ MIKE CLEARS THROAT ]
Whats the matter with it ?
Said it was flat . No flavor .
- Do they want something else ? MIKE : Yeah .
The check .
Let me taste it .
The customer is an asshole . The bourguignon is good .
MOLLY : Hold on .
You mind if I come in ?
Yeah . Sure .
Thanks .
I thought you 'd be working tonight .
Yeah . You know , I worked the first shift , but ...
there was something else I needed to do .
[ WHISTLING ]
- Can I ... ? - Oh .
Yeah . Sure , go ahead .
[ THUNDER RUMBLES ]
Thank you .
Listen ...
When everything started going down on that bridge ...
the only thing I thought about was you .
Getting you to safety .
You are the only thing I care about , Molly .
Whatever 's wrong , I can fix it .
You haven 't done anything wrong .
Then , what ? What is it ?
Paris .
We talked about that .
I 'm not going to uproot my life , leave you , for that job .
But it 's the only thing you 've ever dreamed of .
Life is too short , Sam .
You have to go after what you love .
I am .
You should take the job .
Go to Paris .
- Hey . CANDICE : Hey .
What 's the matter ?
I don 't know . I 'm not ready . I don 't feel ready .
It 's been really hard to concentrate after everything .
Yeah ? Are you sure ?
Yeah .
Because this is the last practice before the championship .
And it 's your last practice of your college career .
CANDICE : I know , but ...
I think you got this .
- Really ? PETER : Yeah .
I mean , you love it out there .
Okay . You 're right .
And besides , coach would kill me . Heh .
Yeah .
Here .
Thanks .
Come here .
Bye .
PETER : You got this .
MAN 1 : You have to get a little more speed . You gotta hit that follow-up .
GIRL 1 : I 'm sore from the back extensions . GIRL 2 : Really ?
Okay , seriously , this is stupid .
They 've gotta make it cooler or we 're gonna pass out .
They 're working on it .
CANDICE : Well , they should have it fixed by now .
[ BEEPING ]
COACH : Come on , Candice . You 're up .
PETER : Come on , Candice . You got this .
COACH : Candice , now .
MAN 1 : Really strong value on this .
GIRL 3 : Hey , coach ! How was that ?
MAN 1 : I wanna see you guys run the routine all the way through once .
- That 's good . - Whew .
MAN 1 : All right , Janine next . Let 's go .
Let 's go , ladies , and drink water .
That 's it .
Every time , Candice .
- There you go . - Thanks .
COACH : Nicely done , Candice .
Okay , go to bars .
WOMAN : Come on . Hit the floor . You can do it .
PETER : Go hard this time , Candice .
Let 's be aggressive .
COACH : Here we go , Candice . Stay loose .
MAN 2 : Okay , Porter , it 's your turn .
Stay focused .
MAN 3 : Good .
COACH : Looking good , Candice .
[ SCREAMING ]
[ YELLING ]
[ GIRLS SCREAMING ]
Candice ? Candice ' ? !
GIRL 4 : Oh , what happened ? MAN 1 : Don 't touch her .
COACH : Someone call 911 .
Candice ?
[ AMBULANCE SIREN BEEPS ]
[ CHATTERING ]
Peter .
I came as soon as I heard .
She was doing great .
She was almost finished with her routine and then ...
Why did it happen ?
This doesn 't make any sense .
I don 't know , man .
I 'm sorry . I 'm so sorry , Peter .
Let 's just go , Sam .
Hey .
How 's it going ?
It 's weird .
Being here , I mean .
It 's just so quiet .
Yeah , well , Dennis had all the calls rerouted to corporate .
Yeah , well , it 's depressing .
Holy crap . Did you guys get your bereavement pay yet ?
Hey , what 's he doing here ?
I think he just needed the distraction .
Yeah .
Yeah , that 's a bummer about Candice .
Guess we all should have seen that coming .
What ?
You see the crazy shit those gymnasts do . I 'm surprised it doesn 't happen more often .
MAN [ OVER SPEAKERPHONE ] : Once you 've handled the e-mail ...
you 'll need to deactivate all the key cards of the deceased employees .
Instructions are in your binder .
Well , shouldn 't that be the job of the facility manager ?
The facility manager 's dead .
[ SIGHS ]
Dennis , you want me to fly someone up there ?
No , no , I got it .
Aw , Debbie .
You were so naughty .
[ COINS JINGLING ]
Fuck it .
Robert , my man .
OW .
Shit .
You shouldn 't have , buddy .
Hey , man , what are you doing up here ?
Had to get off the factory floor , man . Roy 's driving me crazy .
So , uh , who wants one ?
Where 'd you get these ?
I stole it out of Roy 's truck . Ha , ha. it 's good , right ? Ha , ha .
I got something better .
OLIVIA : Ooh , nice one .
Yeah , count me in .
Are you sure you wanna share that ?
If I don 't , I 'll end up drinking it alone , which is just sad .
Well , this day just got way more fun .
No , I did call you .
Of course . I just called you right now , didn 't I ?
Because I really do wanna take you out again .
Yeah , yeah , we 'll do , like , a nice romantic dinner .
You know , somewhere maybe outside the city .
Hold up .
You know what ? I gotta go .
No , no , no . I 'm not blowing you off .
Hey , listen . Hey , who 's my girl , Kimber ?
Amber , yes , that 's what I said .
Excuse me .
Amber ? Amber , I 'm sorry , wait a second . Is that weird sound on your end or mi ... ?
Sorry about that . My , uh , sister tends to get a little chatty sometimes .
- Uh-huh . - Uh-huh .
So tell me about stress relief .
And what does this really get me ?
This covers a session for two different physical therapies .
Like massage therapy ?
Erotic massage ?
This is a family operation . Everyone on staff is professional .
Hey , that 's great . I prefer a professional . In fact , you know what ? I kind of demand it .
I 'm just trying to clarify , though , that this professional experience ends , uh ...
[ WHISPERS ] ... happy .
I know exactly what you need .
[ IN NORMAL VOICE ] Oh , I 'm sure you do .
- Follow me , please . - I 'd love to .
Whoa , whoa , whoa .
Slow down there a little bit .
Yeah . Yeah , you have a lovely little Canter .
[ ISAAC CHUCKLING ]
Yum yum , dim sum .
Hold up there a second .
All right , these are solid . Just making sure .
Tend to be a bit noisy , if you know what I mean .
Ha , ha . Yo , Buddha . Slow down on the rice cakes .
- Just close your eyes . - Mm-hm .
- Relax . - Ooh .
And Someone will be in to service you soon .
Oh , yeah .
[ MOANS ]
Feels dynamite .
No , no . You 're going the wrong way there , little lady .
[ CHO SPEAKING IN CHINESE ]
Oh .
Wait a second , what happened to the younger version of you ?
Okay , I 'm sorry . Do you come with subtitles ?
[ IN CHINESE ]
Maybe I should go .
Don 't know what that means . No idea . Yep .
OW !
Fuck !
No , no , that 's okay . That 's okay , I 'm all right .
Holy shit , you 're strong .
CHO :
What are you doing ? Ow .
You 're a little aggressive .
What 's " capay " ? I don 't know what that means .
I don 't want a " foo-hay . " No " foo-hay . " Aah !
[ SCREAMS ]
[ ISAAC SOBBING ]
ALL : Cheers .
OLIVIA : Mm .
[ CELL PHONE RINGING ]
Shit , that 's my ride .
Shit . I gotta go .
SAM : Leaving more for us .
[ GLASS BREAKS ]
SAM : All right , well , more for me .
All right , bye .
- See you later . - Okay .
Later .
This is the end , so , what are we toasting to ?
To , uh , finding new jobs .
Because it 's only a matter of time before they shut us down .
- Hear , hear . - Oh . To starting over .
SAM : Peter ?
It just doesn 't make sense .
She dies doing something that she 's done ...
almost every day for the last 15 years of her life .
She said she didn 't wanna do it .
She said she wasn 't ready .
And I should have stopped her .
I should have done something . I should 've ...
Peter , there wasn 't anything you could 've done .
How do you know ?
[ GLASS SHATTERS ]
I 'm sorry . I 'm sorry .
Hello , Agent Block ? This is Dennis .
Yeah , Peter just freaked out about something , I don 't know what .
Does that mean anything ?
[ OVER PHONE ] You told me to call if I saw anything odd .
I don 't know yet , but thank you , Dennis , and call me if you see anything strange .
Stranger .
Should we maybe have code names for one another , do you think ?
Over and out .
All right , ahem , show me how this happened .
I don 't think I can .
BLOCK : What do you mean ?
I mean , I could try it a hundred times and never re-create exactly what happened here .
This is some freaky shit .
[ WATER DRIPS ]
[ ISAAC SCREAMS ]
ISAAC : God !
[ ISAAC GROANING ]
Oh , that actually felt great .
[ IN CHINESE ]
Oh , yeah . Awesome .
Oh ...
Wait . Are those things even sterilized ?
No , no . I 'm not catching any diseases unless I 've earned them .
[ ISAAC SCOFFS ]
Wait a second . You understood that .
You speak English .
[ CHUCKLING ]
Oh .
All right , you know what ?
Let 's do this . Two billion people can 't be Wong .
I said Wong . You follow me ?
You get it , you 're Chinese .
[ ISAAC YELPING ]
Ow , ow . Okay , it 's in. it 's definitely in . Ow , okay , yes , it is in .
How many of these are you gonna put in me ?
[ CELL PHONE BUZZING ]
Oh , uh , hey , can you grab that for me ? Thanks .
Hey .
That 's not very nice , you know .
Okay , your thumbs are kind of in my eyes .
I 'm not gonna lie , it 's a little annoying .
Once again , Chinese lady , I don 't have a clue what you 're saying .
[ IN ENGLISH ] Thirty minutes . You sleep .
Sleep .
Oh .
Hey ! Fire !
Hello ? !
Hey !
Hey ! Hey !
Hey , there 's a fire in here !
Hey , there 's a fire !
Get in here !
[ GASPS ]
[ GRUNTING ]
[ WHIMPERING ]
[ CELL PHONE BUZZING ]
[ GASPS ]
Oh , shit .
[ SCREAMING ]
[ SIGHING ]
[ SCREAMS ]
SAM : You should come with me .
To Paris ?
Yeah , you know , you said it yourself . Like , you 're gonna have to start over .
Start over with me .
How many drinks have you had ?
Enough . Molly , I 'm serious .
Look , you were right . If I don 't take the job , I 'll regret it .
But I 'm not willing to lose you .
Why does it have to be one or the other ?
I 'm better when you 're with me .
Uh , guys , you 're not gonna believe this .
They 're saying it was a freak accident .
Yeah , raise your hand if you believe that .
Who dies during a massage ? Seriously .
PETER : First Candice , now Isaac .
It can 't be a coincidence .
It 's not .
Where are you going ?
NATHAN : It 's that creepy dude .
SAM : Why are you following us ?
Who are you ?
You were at the cemetery , then the gym , now here .
What are you doing ?
My job .
[ BLUDWORTH WHISTLING ]
SAM : What 's happening to us ?
What makes you think I know anything ?
SAM : You warned us .
At the memorial service . You said Death didn 't like to be cheated .
It 's just that I 've seen this before .
Well , that doesn 't do me any good . Heh , heh .
A lucky few survive a disaster .
And then one by one , Death comes for them all .
You changed things on that bridge .
There 's a wrinkle in reality . And that wrinkle is you .
So , what , we 're doomed to die ?
I mean , is that it ?
We just got our lives back , so , what kind of fucked up karma is that ?
- Where is she ? ! - I 'm not gonna let you hurt her , Peter .
You were supposed to die on that bridge .
You 're not supposed to be here .
You shorted Death .
So you let Death have somebody else in your place ...
and then you take their spot in the realm of the living .
All the days and years that they have yet to live .
And they take your place in death .
Then the books are balanced .
Wait a minute . We kill someone , we get their life ? Is that what you 're telling me ?
I don 't make the rules .
I just clean up after the game is over .
[ ENGINE STARTS ]
Maybe that 's why Candice and Isaac are dead .
They weren 't supposed to survive , and now it 's coming after the rest of us .
No .
No , not all of us .
Molly made it , she didn 't die .
What ?
Well , when I had that vision , or premonition , or whatever it was ...
I got you across before the bridge collapsed .
You survived .
You saved her ?
Why , because you decided that she deserved to live more than the rest of us ?
That 's not what he 's saying . I don 't deserve to live more than anyone .
You deserve to live more than Candice .
Whoa , Peter , hang on .
NATHAN : No , look , guys , come on .
You 're not drinking the Kool-Aid , are you ?
Killing people to survive Death 's list . Really ?
I may not know what 's going on , but it 's not what that guy 's selling .
Yeah ? What else is it , then ?
Shit .
We need to tell Olivia .
Come on .
OLIVIA : My forms are all signed .
MAN : I see that it 's been quite a while since your first consultation .
What made you decide to take the leap today ?
Uh , well , a lot is going on in my life ...
and I just don 't wanna miss anything ...
you know , important .
Same reason I had it done myself .
- Come on in back . Let 's get you started . - Okay .
Oh .
LEONOTTI : Yep , that 's the first step . You 'll never need those again .
[ OLIVIA CHUCKLES ]
Here we are . Come on in .
What 's with these ?
Oh , just for some of our younger patients .
And , um , sometimes our older ones too . Come on .
[ DRONING ]
What was that ?
Relax .
You know , it looks a lot worse than it really is .
Okay , I 'm gently going to position your head ...
and I want you to tell me ...
when this feels snug .
I can 't move my head .
Perfect . Just what we want .
There we go .
Okay , now comes the fun part . Here comes a drop .
And you will feel a little numbness in your eye ...
which is a good thing .
Deep breath .
Relax .
Very good .
Thattagirl .
There .
That 's not so bad , is it ?
Looks good .
[ CREAKING ]
- What was that ? - Just relax , Olivia .
I 'm just gonna enter some data into ...
Dottie !
Dot ...
Do you know what ? My assistant 's given me an incomplete file .
I 'll be right back .
OLIVIA : Hold on , you 're leaving ? !
[ BEEPING ]
Is that supposed to be happening ? !
[ BEEPING FASTER ]
[ WHIMPERING ]
[ MACHINE WHIRRING ]
[ SCREAMING ]
Help me !
Olivia Castle . Where is she ?
SAM : She might be in danger .
She 's fine . We do this kind of procedure all the time .
[ OLIVIA SCREAMING ]
[ SOBBING ]
Help me !
[ SCREAMING ]
DOTTIE : This has never happened before .
[ DOTTIE DETECTIVE SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY ]
Sam .
Stay with me tonight , please .
Of course .
Five different systems had to go wrong ...
for that laser to fail us so spectacularly . Five .
What do you want from us ?
I want you to tell me what you think is going on .
Two deaths ? Okay , all right . That 's a coincidence .
Three ? That 's a pattern .
Now ...
I know you two didn 't do this .
All right ?
But I think you know something .
What is it ?
We don 't know anything .
Take a guess .
We think we weren 't supposed to survive on that bridge .
What ?
And now something is trying to set it right .
" Something " ?
That 's all you got ?
SAM : Right now , yeah .
But if you come up with any other explanations , let us know .
Thank you .
" Something . "
Hey .
Been up long ?
Uh , I don 't know . I couldn 't sleep . I just kept thinking about the bridge .
Sam , you can 't do this to yourself .
No . No , no , no . I was thinking about , in the premonition ...
we all got off the bus , but the ground gave way and Candice fell .
Then the bus tipped over .
And Isaac , he never got off the bus . He went with it .
What are you getting at ?
I know that there was just so much going on ...
Look , I know that I helped you across .
Then I reached back for Olivia .
But she didn 't make it . She fell .
So first was Candice .
[ SCREAMS ]
Then Isaac .
Then Olivia .
[ SCREAMS ]
They 're dying in order .
Who dies after Olivia ?
[ SIGHS ]
NATHAN [ OVER PA ] : Roy , would you come to the control room , please ?
MAN : Uh-oh , Roy , that 's the boss . You in trouble , Roy .
ROY : Okay , schoolboy , what do you wanna talk to me about ?
NATHAN : What is with your timecard ? ROY : Let 's talk about my timecard .
You out my hours , which means you cut my pay !
I cut everyone 's hours , okay ?
Corporate has us operating at less than 50 percent until this thing blows over .
My bookie ain 't operating at 50 percent .
- My dumb kid ain 't operating at 50 percent . - Roy .
My ex-wife , she 's taking 50 percent , so I 'll tell you what I 'm gonna do .
No , we gotta move , man .
ROY : Hey , I 'm not going anywhere . Hey ! NATHAN : Look , we gotta move ! Gotta move !
We gotta move now !
[ ROY GRUNTS THEN SCREAMS ]
NATHAN : Roy ! You okay down there ?
- Hey , Dennis ? DENNIS : Hey .
They 're closing us down .
They 're shutting down the plant ?
Not the plant , just us . Just sales and administration .
Can you believe it ? Us ?
It 's the factory guys that usually get laid off .
Not us , we 're supposed to be safe .
Yeah , Dennis , we got bigger problems .
Olivia and Isaac are dead .
Who 's Isaac ?
Isaac Palmer , tech support .
Wasn 't he dead already ?
No , Dennis .
Listen , it 's going to happen to us too if we don 't do something about it .
Yeah , I understand . Listen , it 's called survivor 's guilt .
No . No , guilt doesn 't kill you .
Obviously , you 've never met my in-laws .
I 'm not fucking around here , Dennis .
Anyone could be next .
It could be you . Understand ?
Nobody 's safe .
What are you talking about ?
We weren 't supposed to survive that bridge collapse .
And so now it 's kill or be killed .
You get that , Dennis ?
Whatever .
I warned you . Do whatever you wanna do .
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
I Will .
Hey , Agent Block , it 's Dennis . Um ...
Listen , Pete just came in here and he 's just completely lost it .
He 's yelling about " kill or be killed . "
Oh , yeah , it definitely sounded like a threat .
What happened ?
NATHAN : I don 't know . I don 't know . It just happened so fast .
- Nathan . Are you okay ? - Yeah .
- We heard , and we thought ... - No . No , uh , I 'm good .
Did you kill him ?
What ?
No . No , I just ...
It was just timing , you know ? He got in the way and ...
No , you did , didn 't you ?
You saw it coming , and then you took his life . You put him in the way .
No , I didn 't really do anything .
- Tell us the truth : Did you or didn 't you ? - Hey , Peter , calm down .
Did you or didn 't you ?
Yes . I think I did .
I killed him .
So if the theory works , then you traded spots .
He should have your death , and you should have his years .
How do we know for sure ?
I think there 's an order to these deaths .
They mirror the order everyone died in on the bridge .
Then who would be next ?
Who wants to be first to tell me what the hell happened ?
Who is it , Sam ?
Who 's what ?
[ ALL GASPING ]
Dennis ! It was Dennis .
No shit .
MAN : Jesus .
Why are you fighting me on this ?
You 're not seriously going to work , are you ?
Molly , Isaac died on a massage table .
If Death is gonna come for me , I don 't think it matters where I am .
You have to do something .
- What , kill someone so I can live ? - No , of course not .
We 'll just have to figure something else out .
I have figured it out .
Something saved me on that bridge .
Maybe it doesn 't want me to die .
Maybe .
We can 't live our lives in fear , Moll .
So if it happens tomorrow , or 50 years from now , whatever .
As long as we 're together ...
I 'll be okay .
Right ? Why don 't you come by after my shift ...
and I 'll make you a nice late dinner , okay ?
All right , give me this .
[ SIGHS ]
[ CHATTERING ]
WOMAN : Excuse me . We don 't have to wait for them , do we ?
HOSTESS : I 'll let you know . WOMAN : Okay , thank you .
[ TERRY POISON 'S " GIRL ON THE RUN " PLAYING ON SPEAKERS ]
To the girl on the run
[ SINGER SINGING IN FRENCH ]
COOK 1 : Veal 's ready , take it out .
Samuel . Get to work on the bourguignon .
[ SPEAKING IN FRENCH ]
Whoa .
COOK 2 : Pan coming through .
COOK 3 : Whoa , watch yourself .
MANAGER : Okay . Meat 's in . Pick it up , eh ? COOK 4 : Yes , sir .
Whoa .
That could 've been ugly , huh ? Ha , ha .
Yeah . Could 've been .
Vincent , speed it up , okay ?
SAM : Whoa , hey !
[ SPUTTERING ]
[ SIGHS ]
CHEF : Hey , clean that grate .
- Just met your girlfriend . - Oh .
Are you sure it 's okay if I make her a little something ?
Make sure to clean up afterward .
I will , of course . Thank you .
And , chef ...
[ SPEAKS IN FRENCH ]
The apprenticeship .
If the offer still stands ...
I 'd like to take it .
It 's yours .
[ WOMAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY OVER RADIO ]
SAM : Okay , no more suspense .
[ MOLLY CHUCKLES ]
What you 've been waiting for .
Wow . You 're gonna help me with this , right ?
Yeah , sure , if you want me to ...
No ? You don 't want me to ... ?
So how 's your French ?
Heh . Terrible .
Oh , good . Well , then , we can be terrible together .
- Why ? - I took the internship .
What ? Sam , that 's amazing .
I 'm so proud of you .
- Peter . - Hey .
You okay , man ? You look a little , uh , upset .
Yeah . Yeah , yeah , yeah . Just a rough couple days .
Yeah . Yeah , for everyone .
For some more than others .
Do you mind if I come in ?
Oh , yeah , of course . Yeah , come in .
Here , have a seat .
Thanks .
Hey , Peter .
Hi , Molly .
Peter , can I get you anything to eat ? I can make you up some pasta .
Uh , no . No , no , no . I 'm good . Uh , thank you .
Uh , I 'm sorry . I just thought ...
It 's good that you 're here . You shouldn 't be alone right now .
Yeah , you know , I 'm surprised I 'm here at all .
Uh ...
Still alive , I mean .
I 'm next to go , right ?
It 's me and then you , isn 't it ?
Anyways , uh , I was up all last night , you know ...
thinking about if I could really do it .
- Do what ? - Take someone else 's life .
If I could actually kill some stranger , replace their life with my own .
And I thought about it .
And I convinced myself that ...
yeah , I could .
So I went on a walk .
You know , nowhere in particular ...
but every couple of minutes , an opportunity would just present itself
Heh . Like clockwork .
I could just grab somebody and pull them into an alley .
Or just shove somebody off a curb into traffic .
You know ?
It 'd be real easy .
Peter , what did you do ?
- Did you ... ? - No , I didn 't .
I couldn 't .
I realized that ...
I couldn 't kill somebody that didn 't deserve to die .
And I thought about Candice , and I thought , " Wait a minute .
Candice didn 't deserve to die .
Olivia didn 't . Dennis didn 't .
I don 't . "
Do I ?
No , of course you don 't .
Well ...
none of us deserve to die , then why is it ...
that you deserve to live , Molly ?
You said it yourself ...
you don 't .
[ GUNSHOT ]
Go !
Repeat , shots fired . Requesting backup . 1026 Washington .
Hide and I 'll distract him . When you can , go .
PETER : Not done yet , Sam .
Where is she ?
- Where is she ? ! - I 'm not gonna let you hurt her , Peter .
You 're gonna have to kill me first .
Well , that doesn 't do me any good . Heh , heh .
Death 's after you too .
This is crazy , Peter . Don 't do this .
Just think for a minute , all right ?
You are not a killer .
I don 't wanna kill anybody , Sam .
I don 't wanna die yet either .
[ BOTH GRUNT ]
Heh . It 's not your time yet .
Don 't worry , Molly ...
I didn 't kill him .
But I didn 't need to , Molly ...
because Death is gonna do that for me .
Doesn 't mean I can 't help it .
That 's it .
- Are you okay ? What 's going on ? - It 's Peter . He has a gun .
[ GUNFIRE ]
Oh , my God .
You killed him .
It 's Sam 's turn .
MOLLY : Peter , just go .
You have Block 's life , you 're safe now .
Please .
I 'm sorry , Molly .
But you just witnessed the murder of a federal agent .
And I 'm not gonna spend the life I just earned in prison .
[ MOLLY SCREAMS ]
[ BOTH GRUNTING ]
Molly , go ! Go get help !
You son of a bitch !
Tell Candice I love her .
Peter .
It 's gone . You killed him .
So does that mean I get Block 's life ?
[ MOLLY SCREAMS ]
Yeah .
I guess I do .
Do you mind if I take the window seat ?
- You 're gonna make me sit in the middle ? - Uh-huh .
SAM : I 'm like twice your size . - Not really .
- All right . MAN 1 : Sit down .
MAN 2 : I 'll remove him . GUY : Fuck you . I 'll remove myself .
GIRL : Get off him !
Settle down !
- Come on , Browning ! Come on , you punk ! - Get off the plane !
Get off the plane . You don 't understand !
LEWTON : Everybody just stay where you are .
- What 's all that about ? - I have no idea .
PILOT [ OVER PA ] : Ladies and gentlemen , we 'll be pulling away from the gate as ...
[ STATIC CRACKLES OVER PA ]
MOLLY : Here we go .
WOMAN 1 [ OVER PA ] : The cabin lights have been dimmed for takeoff
[ MAN 3 SPEAKING IN FRENCH OVER PA ]
[ KANSAS ' " DUST IN THE WIND " PLAYING ON HEADPHONES ]
With curiosity
Dust in the wind
[ MOLLY GASPS ]
Sorry about that .
WOMAN 2 : Oh , excuse me .
Those passengers who got off the plane earlier , what was that all about ?
FLIGHT ATTENDANT : A kid had a panic attack and wanted off the plane .
Said he had some kind of vision .
No .
Oh , my God !
[ PASSENGERS SCREAMING ]
Sam .
[ SCREAMING ]
[ MOLLY SCREAMING ]
SAM : I got you !
- Sam ! - Molly , hold on !
No !
[ SCREAMS ]
[ SAM SCREAMING IN SLOW MOTION ]
[ KANSAS ' " DUST IN THE WIND " PLAYING ON SPEAKERS ]
[ CROWD CHATTERING ]
Nice of you to come , Nathan .
I know Roy wasn 't the easiest guy to work with .
You know .
I still can 't believe he 's gone , though .
Yeah . Yeah , no kidding .
I guess it was for the best .
What do you mean ?
Company did an autopsy for insurance purposes .
Turns out Roy had an enlarged blood vessel in his brain so big ...
it was about to burst . They said he 'd be dead any day now .
[ OVER SPEAKERS ] Nothing lasts forever but the ...
Any day ?
Life 's a bitch .
Dust in the wind
[ SCREAMS ]
[ TIRES SCREECH ]
[ G-ROANS ]
[ MUFFLED SCREAM ]
[ SCREAMS ]
[ YELLS ]
BLUDWORTH : You all just be careful now .
[ English - Us - SDH ]